Congratulations on this
momentous occasion!
You boys came very close
to missing the cutoff date.
But there's no doubt,
what you brought us is the third place
lottery ticket worth five million yen!
And with that being said,
take this, it's the promissory note you'll
use to receive the five million yen.
It's standard procedure.
Please allow us three days to process
before collecting your winnings.
Holy wilders.
One, ten, hundred, thousand? What?
It's got six zeros.
Ha-ha-ha!
Thank you.
Now then, if you gentlemen don't mind,
there's something I'd like to ask you.
It's regarding your winning ticket.
Refresh my memory, if you would.
Which store did you say
you procured it from?
You want to know where we got it?
Why would you want to
know something like that?
Is there a problem?
No, it's a simple formality.
You understand.
Dim-witted ding-dongs, you expect me to
believe you won five million yen? Please!
My teller senses have never failed me
and you hoodlums reek of foul play!
Dear me, what's this?
Am I sensing hesitation? Odd.
Oh no, your question just
caught me off guard is all.
We bought the ticket in Morioh.
Really?
Well, I have to tell you
that's very peculiar.
Not a single store in Morioh
sells lottery tickets,
so I find your story hard to swallow.
Huh?
Oh, yeah. That's right.
We must have picked it up when
we went to a city the other day.
Of course, it's all coming back to me.
We bought so much stuff that day.
I totally forgot what he said.
It was so long ago.
You know.
While we're on the subject,
I found another discrepancy.
If you look on the reverse side of the.
You'll find spaces for the ticket holder.
to write in their name
and telephone number.
Ichiro Morishita.
And unless I'm losing my eyesight,
the name written here doesn't seem
to match any of yours, does it?
There's a name written on the back?
And a phone number, too!
Oh, jeez, how did none of us
remember to check for that stuff?
Just ignore him.
Me, oh my, you've found yourselves
in quite the peculiar predicament.
Is this your lottery ticket or not?
I want an honest answer.
Oh, yeah, I know what happened.
A friend gave me his new number, and I
guess I accidentally wrote it on the back.
Friend, eh?
Well, why didn't you say so?
We'll give Mr.
Morishita a ring and get this entire
mess cleared up lickety-split.
It might interest you, gentlemen,
to know all lottery
tickets are traceable to
their point of purchase
via their serial number.
If this Ichiro Morishita
fellow did indeed purchase
a lottery ticket and can
remember where he bought it,
we'll be obliged to confirm his signature.
It's a tedious process, but
vital for security purposes.
To whom does this
mysterious ticket belong?
Depending on our findings, we may have
to turn it over to the police. What?
The police?
Morishita speaking.
Who is it?
Hello, sir.
I'm a teller at Budogaoka Bank.
I have a question only
you can answer. Did a Mr.
Morishita recently purchase a
great year-end lottery ticket?
Yeah, I'm Ichiro Morishita.
I bought the little sucker.
No doubt about it.
Yes!
Now I've got you
dunder-headed delinquents!
I knew you were lying through your teeth!
Hell would freeze over before the gods
bestowed the winning ticket on pathetic,
money-grubbing goons like you!
And you're sure, sir?
You're positive you bought a ticket?
Sure, didn't you hear me?
I must have bought ten of
them, but would you know it?
They're all duds.
Well, except for this one
Normally, I changed the whole
thing, but this ought to do it
We will need a signature mr.
Kinoshita, but the ticket
is all yours Kinoshita?
My name's Morishita.
Oh
What I don't understand I could have
sworn it was the character for Mariah Uh,
your phone number is 1771-1281,
correct, Mr. Kinoshita?
I told you, my name's Morishita, pinhead.
Why are you even wasting
my time with this bullshit?
Maybe you should try selling me a winner
instead of bugging me over the damn phone.
So sorry to trouble you.
This isn't over yet.
You boys wait right there.
The number you have reached
is no longer in service.
Please check the number
of your desired party.
We told you that the ticket was ours.
Tell her, man.
Please accept my congratulations
and deepest apologies.
Whoo! Happy day!
I got my money!
It was a lot of hard work, but now
I'm five million years richer. Hey!
What is that supposed to mean?
You promised we'd get half
of that lottery money!
Shigechi!
Huh? Uh...
Did I say that? I don't recall.
Yeah, you're gonna try
and pull that shit again.
Yeah, what are you doing?
Josuke?
Why are you holding me back?
Don't tell me you're letting this
roly-poly shit back get away with it.
Oh, no He's not getting
off scot-free this time.
Oh, this kid's gloves
are coming off Shigechi
Now that's what I'm talking about.
I knew you wouldn't
back down from a fight,
especially when there's
so much on the line So you
just up and decided not to
split the money anymore.
Is that it?
Sorry, but that's not going to fly
when it comes to this kind of cash.
Here.
This should get you two
beggars off my back.
It's not like you did anything
to deserve this money.
Think of this handout as a pity payment
from your friendly neighborhood...
Whoa! Son of a...
No, Okuyasu, don't!
You jerk off! Give it here!
You promised us half the winnings,
so half is what we're gonna get!
Don't make me say it again!
You got up easy today, greedy bastard!
You always go straight
to using your fists.
You gotta control yourself.
Tonkin wasn't gonna work on him, so I
thought some manhandling would do the trick.
You're not hurt too bad, are you?
I want to apologize for Okuyasu.
He never should have hit you.
But this just proves it.
Our partnership isn't working out, so I
think we'll hold on to the promissory note.
That'll be the best move
for everyone involved.
We'll cash it in three days as planned.
After that's done, we'll split the money
the way we said, and you'll get half.
Good riddance.
I am so over that asshole.
There's no way in hell you'll catch
me hanging out with that guy anymore.
I hear you.
But when you stop to think about it,
we were the ones trying to
exploit him for pocket money.
We should consider what
that says about us.
You moron. Huh?
That's not how I see
this situation at all.
The only reason he got his filthy mitts on
the five million was
because we helped him.
Without us, he'd be lucky
to even get a few thousand.
But instead, he gets to walk
away with 2.5 million yen!
2.5 million yen!
It stays with me.
The ticket stays with me.
I heard everything, you sneaky douche-bro!
Neither of you is getting a single
yen of my hard-earned winnings!
We got that five million because
of Harvest's amazing ability!
Huh?
You scrubs and your puny stands
are nothing compared to my Harvest!
Want me to prove it to ya?
We can go at it right
now, what do you say?
Let's get it on!
Why you... Freaking great!
It took the IOU for the money!
You're pissing off the wrong
stand users, pineapple head!
Follow me and I won't
hesitate to kill you.
So back the hell off.
Shigechi...
I'm pretty sure this fool just
said he was gonna kill us.
If you're so big and bad,
sit your stand on us already!
But the second you do, get
ready to be ripped apart!
We got a problem Joe skate.
What is it something where
it's happening in my pants?
My legs there's something making my
legs it's like a son of a bitch bitch.
Can't you take care of that later?
I don't know you tell me
What is happening to me?
You have to roll up
your pants Okuyasu hurry
How did these freaky
things get in my pants?
Damn, it's no use.
Knocking just a few of
them off is pointless.
We're gonna have to come at
this from a different angle.
Aw, damn it.
Look, he's getting away.
All right, he's really
starting to piss me off.
Join the club.
The guy's been pissing me off all day.
We're coming for you, money.
Just hold on a second.
This backstabber's about
to learn the hard way what
happens to thieving punks
who cross the Josuyasu duo.
No one makes a fool out of Okuyasu
the Great and gets away with it.
I'll beat him till he's black and blue.
At least now we know he's
not just a greedy bastard.
He's a complete idiot too.
That Butterball may be
slippery but there's no way
he'll be able to run long
enough to get away from us I
Told you look at the little dumbass
It's like he's a tank and
harvest is moving underneath
them like some kind of
a dark caterpillar trap
Actually, it's more like a bucket
really expecting that kind of speed.
We gotta close the distance
He's not the brightest boat, but he's
actually kind of clever in a weird way.
It's like he's acting on pure instinct.
Oh no! He got away! Don't panic yet.
I got a trick up my sleeve.
He's gonna have his stand do all the heavy
lifting, then we'll just follow suit.
That money's not getting away!
I get it!
It's mine now, five million yen.
Did you really think you could
weasel away from us, Shigechi?
Why don't you make Harvest
attack us again, pork you prick?
I can't wait to pop each and every one
of your messed up little mini-me's.
You've seen firsthand how
amazing my Harvest is.
It can collect anything large or small.
Even the screws that hold pipes together!
And don't forget the balls!
Good plan,
but I think you're forgetting about how
Bites my Shining Diamond's power is!
What's up, friend?
You've done a real good job
of getting on my bad side,
but I'm still willing to forgive you.
First, I want to rearrange
that ugly mug of yours, though.
Come on, hand over that
IOU, Shigechi. It's over.
I told you two fools.
If you chased me, then I'd kill you.
What's going on?
My hands are...
Uh, I can't get up.
What's wrong?
Okuyasu, he's up to something!
You can't let your guard down!
You two?
What's he doing?
You mean you haven't figured it out yet?
You two are sloppy drunk
courtesy of this little number.
Is that alcohol?
My harvest can get its hands on
anything I order it to snatch.
So, I had to grab some booze when
we ran past the liquor store.
And when you weren't paying attention,
I injected the hooch into
your stupid lying bodies.
Well, to be more specific, I made
it squirt right into your veins.
Wait, you what?
Aw, get out!
When alcohol goes directly into the veins,
you don't need that much until
you're shit-faced and flailing.
I knew alcohol could be used
as a makeshift anesthetic,
but I never thought a kid
would figure that out?
let alone use it to whammy me like this.
Looks like he's not a
total idiot after all.
No, it must be his instinct again.
Oh, he's dead meat.
I might be a little tipsy, but there's no
way that's gonna stop me from ending you.
My frickin' eye!
What are you waiting for, Josuke? Fix it!
Shit, hang in there!
I'm on it!
If I'm remembering everything correctly,
you two dickwads called me a whole bunch
of shitty names earlier, didn't you?
I'm gonna show you what
happens when you try to pull
the wool over my eyes and
treat me like a dumb kid.
Damn you!
You're standing there
all high and mighty when
you breaking your promise
is what started this!
I've had about all I can take.
Keep this up and you're not
gonna like what comes next.
I think you've done more than enough
talking for one life, jerks gay.
And since your stand's weak, your bite
can't even back up your puny bark.
Actually, both of your stands are shit,
so save the demands until you're
half as strong as Harvest.
Till then, take it in the eye.
Quick, Josuke, close your eye!
You okay?
Damn. So close.
There's no point in
closing your eyes, FYI.
Harvest can grab anything,
no matter the obstacle.
Shut those peepers as tight as you want.
It'll just tear off your
eyelids and gouge out the eye.
We get the point, Shigechi. Stop it.
Just forgive us already.
It's not like we wanted this to happen.
Huh?
Was that an apology?
Damn it, kid.
I have had it with your shitty attitude.
Hear that, Okuyasu?
Josuke seems to be on a completely
different page from you.
Don't worry about him.
He'll come around.
But how about we give you this?
It's the 10,000 yen you gave me, plus
everything else I have on me right now.
Take it as our penance for
all the trouble we've caused.
Police Shigechi, I'm begging
you not to off Josuke.
If he gets taken out, who'll fix my eye?
Oh, Okuyasu!
Huh? Oh, yeah.
I almost forgot I gave
you that little handout.
I felt so bad for you beta boys,
I decided the only right thing to do
was bless you with over 10,000 yen.
Here, the money's all yours.
Just have mercy on us,
old strong one! I...
Way to use your brain.
You're trying to lure him in like
catching a raccoon with a bit of bait.
Once he closes the distance,
bam, you'll let him have it.
Well, I've got your back, buddy.
Go for it, man, work your magic.
That's a good boy.
I don't know where this newfound
obedience is coming from,
but I'm glad you know the pecking order.
Something wonky's going on.
Hey now, Okuyasu,
it feels like you're trying to lure me in
with cash so you can
attack me with your stand.
But you wouldn't do
that, would you, old pal?
No.
So you were trying to trick me.
Did you think I'd honestly fall for a
harebrained scheme as lame as that one?
You must think I'm some kind of idiot.
Well, no pity for you.
It's not like we needed it anyway.
Time's run out for you, little man.
I guess you were too busy
flapping your gums like a dumbass
to realize that you walked right
into the hand-striking range.
I'll claw away the air
and make a teleport,
forcing the ticket out of
your hands and back to us.
This ticket is ours.
It belongs with you.
You know who you're talking to.
Idiots, you wasted your time
because I'm about to take it back.
Incredible, you're even
dumber than I thought.
Your chance of winning just expired
and you never saw it coming.
My money!
What do you think you're
doing to that ticket?
It's worth five million yen and
you're ripping it up like it's trash!
Why would you do that?
I don't get you in the least!
What was the point in going
through all this hoopla if you
were just going to rip it up
when you finally got your way?
Because of you, I needed a surefire way
to stop you from attacking us again.
Since you can't restore the
ticket without my shining diamond,
giving up is your best bet.
The fight's over.
Accept it and stand down.
Oh, I get it now.
That's what you're doing.
And off they go.
Your victory's blowing away in the wind.
I take it all back.
I don't get any of this.
Why would you throw
away five million again?
Have you lost your mind?
Harvest, bring back every last piece. Go!
Holy shit, you really
don't get it, do you?
Sending Harvest on a fetch quest
was the final nail in your coffin.
Your last line of defense is running
through the city looking for paper scraps.
so who's gonna protect you
from these drunks, huh?
I think I get it now.
We did it.
Since I caught you lying down on the job,
why don't we try and get
in a bit of study time?
The scraps of paper floating around
town are picked up by your harvest.
But after that, who has the
power to put them back together?
Hmm?
I need an answer.
Who can put the scraps back
together with Shining Diamond.
You, Josuke. Josuke?
Sounds to me like you're
forgetting something.
Yes, Mr.
Josuke, sir.
Ah, now that's what I like to hear.
And I'm sure you know the name of the
person who recovered that IOU from you.
Well, say his name, Half-Pint.
It's Okuyasu, the Great.
Good, that's our special man.
So, what do you say we change
subjects and do a little math?
How do we split five million
between three people?
And remember, everyone has to be
happy when all is said and done.
Well, I'm fine with half. Half, huh?
Did I or did I not just tell you
there are three of us to consider?
How are each of us supposed to
get half the winnings, Shigechi?
Good thing we're studying because
your math needs some work, dude.
Anyone home?
I guess I'll be okay with a third.
Now that I think about it, without your
help, I'd still be collecting old stamps.
I was acting like a spoiled brat.
We all found that lottery
ticket by working as a team.
If we hadn't banded together, we
never would have pulled it off.
Wow, it's starting to make sense.
My greed kept me from
seeing the big picture.
Let's split everything fair and
square so we all get what we want.
There we go!
I've never seen so much money before!
Five million yen!
If you're interested in a home
for your newly acquired wealth,
your funds would be very
secure at Budogaoka Bank.
You bet we're interested!
We finally did it!
It's like I'm dreaming!
I have a question.
Didn't we agree to split the
winnings between the three of us?
Hear me out.
In the interest of maintaining a fair
and just agreement between us partners,
wouldn't it be best to include
our stands in this deal?
I mean, fair is fair, after all.
And since Harvest is made
up of about 500 mini-stands,
we should split the pot
five hundred to one to one.
That's not an issue, is it? Uh-huh!
You're unbelievable!
I thought you learned your lesson, but
you just don't know when to stop haggling,
do you?
I was only messing
around, a third is fine.
For some, that's far too much
money for high schoolers to have.
But c 'est la vie.
To the arms and the lips and the face.
Of the humic and of all that I need to.
I want to come and stand
a little bit closer.
Breathe in and get a bit higher.
You'll never know what hit you!
When I get to you.
Ooh, I want you.
I don't know if I need you.
Ooh, I got it.
If I know.
Ooh, I want you.
I don't know if I need you.
Ooh, I got it.
If I know.